Context, for every holiday, my mother would ask the women in the family, my sisters, sister-in-law,
my wife, my female cousins, to send samples of the desserts they planned to bring to the
celebration for testing and to see if these desserts could make it to the food menu.
My wife has been complaining about my mother deliberately rejecting every dessert sample
she sent.
So many times my mother has told her that she's being honest and keeping the guests'
best interests at heart.
Yet my wife still thought that my mother is deliberately excluding her since two of her
dessert samples were rejected before.
For this year's Christmas, my mother is doing the same thing, but this time, she told every
woman who are participating to make a cookie sample and send it to her for testing.
My wife took it as a challenge, and to be honest, she worked really hard to make a good
sample and sent it to my mother days ago, and the results just came in yesterday.